ecu.edu.au 2019-06-02

# ECU | Privacy statement : Supplemental

Edith Cowan University recognises and respects your privacy. ECU will deal with personal and health information in a manner that protects the privacy of individuals whilst meeting obligations as may be prescribed by legislation, or as set out in University policy.

In conducting its normal business of teaching, learning, research and recruitment, the University acquires, holds, uses or communicates personal information relating to students, staff or other persons. ECU will treat this information with the highest standards of confidentiality and privacy. Personal information will only be used for the purposes for which you have disclosed it to us. The University will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your express consent unless required to do so by law.

We use third-party advertising technology to serve ads when you visit our website and sites upon which we advertise. In the course of our advertising, unique third-party cookies may be placed on your computer system and accessed by your web browser. You may restrict the use of cookies through your web browser’s settings.

In addition, we use tags, provided by our ad-serving partners, to help manage our online advertising. These tags enable our ad servers to recognize your browser’s cookie when you visit the site and to learn which marketing ads brought you to our website. To learn more about this technology and also how to "opt-out" from its use, please go to <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>.

### Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy covers the following principles

  * Collection and Holding of Personal, Sensitive and Health Information
  * Use and Disclosure of Personal, Sensitive and Health Information
  * Collection and Use of Non-Identifying Information
  * Research – Personal and Health Information
  * Disclosure – Overseas Recipient

Our privacy policy also **includes contact details for key university staff** should you wish to discuss how we keep the information you provide safe and secure. You can view the [privacy policy online](http://www.ecu.edu.au/GPPS/policies_db/policies_view.php?rec_id=0000000335) via our policies webpage.
